fxcc.com 2017-10-31

# FXCC Privacy Policy | How we use information we may collect

At FXCC we understand the importance of maintaining the confidentiality of our clients personal information and are committed to ensuring the security of any information provided by our clients through this website.

#### Collection of Personal Information

In order to provide financial products and services to our clients efficiently and accurately, when you apply to register to use one or more of our services we will ask you for personal information. Required information may include customer’s full name, date of birth, home and work addresses and telephone numbers, email address, passport number/or ID number, marital status, government issued photo ID with signature, financial information such as estimated annual income, net worth, liquid assets, previous trading experience and risk tolerance.

We may also gather certain information about your use of our services. This may include information from which you and/or your company can be identified such as the times you log on, your volume of use of the services, the types of data, systems and reports you access, the locations from which you log on, duration of sessions and other similar data.

#### Uses Made Of Your Personal Information

We gather information to allow us to administer, support, and obtain feedback on our services, to identify and prevent faults with our services and the Site, to improve the services offered by us, to ensure we are maintaining adequate security measures and to prevent any security breaches of our Site, to keep you informed about products and services that may be of interest to you.

We may also use this information, for research and analysis purposes such as monitoring website usage in order to help us develop the Site and improve our services.

#### Further Uses Of Your Personal Information; Marketing

In addition we may process your personal data for marketing purposes and there are several ways in which we may use the personal information you have provided to us, including the following:

  * We may contact you about services to which you do not subscribe which we think may be of interest to you;
  * We may wish to provide you with information about special features of our Site that we think may be of interest to you;
  * We may provide you with information from our affiliates which we think may be of interest to you;
  * We may invite you to client functions or entertainment events; and
  * The above contacts may be via email, fax, post and/or telephone.

If you do not want us to use your personal information in this way, please send an email to [accounts@fxcc.com](mailto:accounts@fxcc.com) asking not to be contacted for any marketing purposes or specifying which of the above you do not wish to be contacted about. Please include your name, address and postcode along with any account number or other reference you may have. If you are an on-line subscriber, you may update your account to amend your marketing preferences at any time.

#### Our Cookie Policy

To provide you with a better experience we sometimes use cookies. A cookie is a text file made up of letters and numbers that allows us to distinguish your browser/device from another visitor's browsers/device without uniquely identifying the individual person using the computer. Cookies are widely used by website owners in order to make their websites work, or to work more efficiently, as well as to provide reporting information.

You have the right to decide whether to accept or reject cookies by setting or amending your web browser controls to accept or refuse cookies. If you choose to reject cookies, you may still use our website though your access to some functionality and areas of our website may be restricted. As the means by which you can refuse cookies through your web browser controls vary from browser-to-browser, you should visit your browser’s help menu for more information.

If you continue to use this website without changing the cookie settings of your web browser then you are consenting to our cookie policy

To learn more about cookies and how to manage them via your browser/device please visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/)

#### Disclosure of your information

We will not without your consent disclose to third parties any individually identifying information, such as names, postal and e-mail addresses, telephone numbers, which you have provided to FXCC.

In some circumstances, we may pass on information to third parties such as our professional advisors, administrators or subcontractors, or to licensors of the software used on the Site.

We may also disclose your personal information to third parties if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation, or in order to enforce or apply our Site Terms and Conditions.

#### Your consent

By submitting your information, you consent to the use by FXCC of that information, as set out in this policy. By accessing and using this you are acknowledging that you have read, understood and agree with this privacy policy. We reserve the right to change our privacy policy from time to time and will update this page accordingly. Please review our policy as often as possible – your continued use of the Site will signify that you agree to any such changes.

The Site may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites may have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites.

#### How we protect your information

FXCC may store your information in its databases for reference in order to answer queries or resolve problems, provide improved and new services and to meet any legal data retention requirements. This means we may retain your information after you stop using the Site or our services or otherwise interacting with us.

All information you provide to us is stored on secure servers. The transmission of information via the internet is secured using Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology with high security 128bit encryption. However we have put in place various security procedures as set out in this policy. Once we have received your information, we will use procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.

#### Failure to Provide Personal Information

You have a choice to supply any or all of the personal information required. However, missing information may result in our being unable to open or maintain your account and /or to provide you with our services.

#### Contact Information

If you would like to contact us with any queries or comments concerning our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us via e-mail, postal address, phone and fax or use our chat facility to IM a customer service representative.

#### Address

FX Central Clearing LTD. (FXCC)  
Amorosa Centre, 2nd floor,  
2 Samou Street, 4043 Yermasoyia  
Limassol, Cyprus 

Tel: +357 25 870 750  
Fax: +357 25 870 753  
E-mail: [info@fxcc.com](mailto:info@fxcc.com)
